Julio Bermudez



julioph0n3@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/julio-bermudez-4b3742251



+17547158059



https://juliobermudez.github.io/Profesional-Portfolio/

Summary

Hello there! I am a Junior Full Stack Web Developer who just graduated from the University of Miami Coding Bootcamp. I take pride in providing clean code and pixel-perfect designs. I have dedicated myself to learning and growing every day, constantly pushing my limits to discover new ways of creating amazing user experiences. If you would like to see some of my work, please check out my Portfolio at https://juliobermudez.github.io/ Profesional-Portfolio/

Experience



DIGITAL SAIZ

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 10 months)

- Use of Node.js and Express.js to create a RESTful API.
- Use of NoSql or MySQL, and the Sequelize ORM for the databases.
- Build a polished UI.
- Use different libraries, packages, or technology depending of the client requirement

Banking Associate

TD

Dec 2022 - Present (11 months)

- Troubleshoot common customer issues related to technology
- Process customer transactions accurately and efficiently maintaining excellent customer service
- Convert customers into loyal clients using consultative selling techniques and build long-term relationships with customers.

Education

University of Miami

Bootcamp, Web Page, Digital/Multimedia and Information Resources Design Jun 2023 - Dec 2023

Universidad de las Artes de Cuba

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Art/Art Studies, General Sep 2012 - Jun 2017

Skills

NoSQL • E-Commerce • WordPress • MySQL • React.js • REST APIs • Back-End Web Development • Software Development • Web Pages • Responsive Web Design